# **Agata Walter**

# **UI/UX DESIGNER**

Designer with 10 years of experience in visual design - 3 years in digital products.

Good interpersonal communication, cross-group collaboration and organizational skills. Passion for design, attention to detail in high quality designs. Open to new challenges & growth in your company.

Phone: 48691303933

Location: Szczecin, Poland / Remote

Mail: agata.a.walter@gmail.com

Web portfolio: <a href="https://angieagava.github.io/portfolio">https://angieagava.github.io/portfolio</a> agavva/

Behance: <a href="https://www.behance.net/agawalter">https://www.behance.net/agawalter</a>

Linkedin: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/agatawalter">https://www.linkedin.com/in/agatawalter</a>

## **EXPERIENCE**

# PRODUCT DESIGNER / UI-UX DESIGNER / GRAPHIC DESIGNER

02/2015 - now (over 7 years) / Freelance

06/2018 - 09/2018 (3 months) Fashion UK platform Shopest / Startup

04/2017 - 10/2017 (6 months) Coding school Netcamp & Infoshare Academy / Small-size company

- Using briefs to develop design criteria.
- Competitor and market analysis to identify unmet needs.
- Designing web and mobile applications, making sketches and developing mockups.
- Creating user flows, wireframes paper to hi-fi and prototypes, developing new features for existing products, working with design systems.
- Cooperation with Frontend and Backend Developers.

#### **OFFICE ADMIN**

# 02/2019 - 05/2021 (2.5 years) Social Cassino HuuugeGames / Corporation

- Creating onboarding documentation, achieving a 70% time reduction in the preparation time of new administration employees.
- Onboarding new office manager in Berlin office in one week, prepered all the necessary documentation.
- Designing and implementing office policies by establishing standards and procedures, measuring results against standards, and achieving a 30% monthly expense reduction.
- Cooperating with supporting & product teams with 95% satisfaction, shown in yearly performance reviews.
- Helped plan and execute weekly, monthly and annual parties, including organizing vendors, researching venues and maintaining guest lists of 50-500 people.

#### **FRONT-END DEVELOPER**

02/2018 - 12/2018 (1 year) Webservices GrupalT / Small-size company

# **FRONT-END MENTOR**

10/2017 - 03/2018 (6 months) Coding school Infoshare Academy / Medium-size company

#### JUNIOR FRONT-END DESIGNER

04/2017 - 03/2018 ( 1year) Online SaaS Platform Wedding.pl / Startup

#### WEB DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP

11/2016 - 02/2017 (3 months) E-commerce platform IAI IdoSell / Corporation

- Coding 50+ full website graphics for online planner.
- Coordinating ad campaigns with graphic and marketing teams.
- Coordinating work between developers, customer service, marketing and PO.
- Supervising weekly changes to Wordpress blog content (HTML, CSS, PHP).
- Knowledge sharing as coach & mentor for juniors in front-end standards.
- Deploying new features and improvements in a quick cycle as part of a collaborative engineering team.

#### **DTP GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

# 02.2014 - 11/2017 (3 years) Print House Copyland Printdream / Small-size company

- Designing and developing branding projects for over 300 customers: logo designs, business cards, marketing and exhibition materials, generating business productivity and growth.
- Meeting with 30 clients per week either in person or online in order to discuss the scope of different projects.
- Coordinating with outside agencies, art services, web designers, marketing as necessary.
- Ensuring 100 % customer satisfaction by presenting art to clients and giving them a chance for feedback.
- Developing documentation to teach new team members company standars and best practices.

# **EDUCATION**

2016 (3 months) Front-end Coding Bootcamp 2010-2014 (4 years) Westpomeranian Technology University / Industrial Design

## **ADDITIONAL**

## **TOOLS:**

Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Creative suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects), W3C validators / Linters, Chrome Dev Tools, Git, IDE, Jira, Invisoin, HTML / CSS / JS, SCSS / SASS, RWD, Wordpress, Bootstrap.

# **SOFT SKILLS:**

Adaptability, ,Collaboration/Teamwork, Problem-solving attitude, Creativity, Analitical Thinking, Empathy, Proactivity,

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

Digital design, Web /mobile design, Print materials, Branding, User research, Competitor analysis, Business analysis, Scrum / Agile methodology, UI/UX knowledge, User flow, Prototyping, Wireframes

#### **CERTIFICATION & TRAINING:**

(2016-2021)Front-End Developer, Mobile App Design: Sketches to Interactive Prototypes User Experience Strategy Fundamentals, Semantic UI, Introduction to Product Management.

## **LANGUAGES:**

Polish (native), English (C2/proficient), German (A2/basic), French (A2/basic).